Department of Mathematics Records UA157
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Exams by course, 1993 -- 2009; 2000 -- 2008; UA157.002; 4.8 Linear Feet
  - Math 18 exam 2 sp, 2007; UA157.002.003.00142 (Box 3)
  - Math 18 exam 3, 2003; UA157.002.003.00143 (Box 3)
  - Math 18 final sp, 2007; UA157.002.003.00144 (Box 3)
  - Math 18 final exam, 2004; UA157.002.003.00145 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam I, 2008; UA157.002.003.00146 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 1, 2008; UA157.002.003.00147 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.003.00148 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.003.00149 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 1, 2005; UA157.002.003.00150 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.003.00151 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.003.00152 (Box 3)
  - Math 2 exam 1 sp, 2003; UA157.002.003.00153 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.003.00154 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam I, 2002; UA157.002.003.00155 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 1, 2001; UA157.002.003.00156 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 1, 2001; UA157.002.003.00157 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 1, 2000; UA157.002.003.00158 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 1, 2000; UA157.002.003.00159 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 2, 2008; UA157.002.003.00160 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.003.00161 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.003.00162 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 2, 2006; UA157.002.003.00163 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 2, 2005; UA157.002.003.00164 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.003.00165 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.003.00166 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 2, 2003; UA157.002.003.00167 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam II, 2003; UA157.002.003.00168 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.003.00169 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.003.00170 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.003.00171 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.003.00172 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 2, 2000; UA157.002.003.00173 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 2, 2000; UA157.002.003.00174 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 3, 2007; UA157.002.003.00175 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 3 (3 versions), 2003; UA157.002.003.00176 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 exam 3, 2000; UA157.002.003.00177 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 final, 2008; UA157.002.003.00178 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 final, 2007; UA157.002.003.00179 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 final, 2007; UA157.002.003.00180 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 final, 2006; UA157.002.003.00181 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 final, 2005; UA157.002.003.00182 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 final exam, 2004; UA157.002.003.00183 (Box 3)
  - Math 22 final exam, 2003; UA157.002.003.00184 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam I, 2008; UA157.002.003.00185 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2008; UA157.002.003.00186 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.003.00187 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.003.00188 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.003.00189 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.003.00190 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2005; UA157.002.003.00191 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2005; UA157.002.003.00192 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.003.00193 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.003.00194 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.003.00195 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.003.00196 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.003.00197 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.003.00198 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2001; UA157.002.003.00199 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2001; UA157.002.003.00200 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2000; UA157.002.003.00201 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 1, 2000; UA157.002.003.00202 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam II, 2008; UA157.002.003.00203 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 2, 2008; UA157.002.003.00204 (Box 3)
  - Math 39 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.003.00205 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.003.00206 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 2, 2006; UA157.002.003.00207 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 2, 2006; UA157.002.003.00208 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 2, 2005; UA157.002.003.00209 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 2, 2005; UA157.002.003.00210 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.003.00211 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.003.00212 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 2, 2003; UA157.002.003.00213 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 2, 2003; UA157.002.003.00214 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.003.00215 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.003.00216 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.003.00217 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.003.00218 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2008; UA157.002.003.00219 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2007; UA157.002.003.00220 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2007; UA157.002.003.00221 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2006; UA157.002.003.00222 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2006; UA157.002.003.00223 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2005; UA157.002.003.00224 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2005; UA157.002.003.00225 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2004; UA157.002.003.00226 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2004; UA157.002.003.00227 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2002; UA157.002.003.00228 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2003; UA157.002.003.00229 (Box Shared 45)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2002; UA157.002.003.00230 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2002; UA157.002.003.00231 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2001; UA157.002.003.00232 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2001; UA157.002.003.00233 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2000; UA157.002.003.00234 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 exam 3, 2000; UA157.002.003.00235 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 final, 2008; UA157.002.003.00236 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 final, 2007; UA157.002.003.00237 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 final, 2007; UA157.002.003.00238 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 final, 2006; UA157.002.003.00239 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 final exam, 2006; UA157.002.003.00240 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 final, 2004; UA157.002.003.00241 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 final exam, 2004; UA157.002.003.00242 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 final exam, 2003; UA157.002.003.00243 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 final exam, 2003; UA157.002.003.00244 (Box 3)
  - Math 38 final exam, 2002; UA157.002.003.00245 (Box 3)
  - Math 41 mid-term fall, 2006; UA157.002.003.00246 (Box 3)
  - Math 46 exam I, 2008; UA157.002.004.00001 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 honors exam 1, 2008; UA157.002.004.00002 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 1, 2008; UA157.002.004.00003 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.004.00004 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.004.00005 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.004.00006 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 honors exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.004.00007 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.004.00008 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - 46c exam 1, 2005; UA157.002.004.00009 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - 46e exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.004.00010 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 1 (both sections), 2004; UA157.002.004.00011 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46c exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.004.00012 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 36e exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.004.00013 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.004.00014 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.004.00015 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.004.00016 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.004.00017 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 1, 2001; UA157.002.004.00018 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam II, 2008; UA157.002.004.00019 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 2, 2008; UA157.002.004.00020 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.004.00021 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.004.00022 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 2, 2006; UA157.002.004.00023 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 2, 2006; UA157.002.004.00024 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46c exam II, 2005; UA157.002.004.00025 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.004.00026 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46c exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.004.00027 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46e exam II, 2004; UA157.002.004.00028 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46e exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.004.00029 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 2, 2003; UA157.002.004.00030 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.004.00031 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.004.00032 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.004.00033 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 1 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.004.00034 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 2, 2000; UA157.002.004.00035 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 3, 2007; UA157.002.004.00036 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 3, 2006; UA157.002.004.00037 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46c ecam III, 2005; UA157.002.004.00038 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam III, 2005; UA157.002.004.00039 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 3, 2001; UA157.002.004.00040 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 exam 3, 2000; UA157.002.004.00041 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 final, 2008; UA157.002.004.00042 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46-01 final, 2007; UA157.002.004.00043 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46-02 final, 2007; UA157.002.004.00044 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 final, 2007; UA157.002.004.00045 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 (1 + 2) final, 2006; UA157.002.004.00046 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 final exam, 2006; UA157.002.004.00047 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46c final, 2005; UA157.002.004.00048 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 462 final, 2004; UA157.002.004.00049 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 final, 2004; UA157.002.004.00050 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46c final exam, 2004; UA157.002.004.00051 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 50mp/193mp (m. 193mp) exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.004.00052 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 50mp exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.004.00053 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 50mp exam 2, 2003; UA157.002.004.00054 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 112, 2002; UA157.002.004.00055 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 112 exam II spring, 2002; UA157.002.004.00056 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 112 exam III spring, 2002; UA157.002.004.00057 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 112 final exam spring, 2002; UA157.002.004.00058 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 128 exam 1 sp, 2004; UA157.002.004.00059 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 128 exam 2 spring, 2004; UA157.002.004.00060 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 exam 1, 2008; UA157.002.004.00061 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.004.00062 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.004.00063 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.004.00064 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.004.00065 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.004.00066 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 exam 1, 2001; UA157.002.004.00067 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 exam II, 2008; UA157.002.004.00068 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.004.00069 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 exam 2, 2006; UA157.002.004.00070 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 exam 2(makeup), 2002; UA157.002.004.00071 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.004.00072 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 final, 2007; UA157.002.004.00073 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 final, 2006; UA157.002.004.00074 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 final, 2004; UA157.002.004.00075 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 final exam, 2003; UA157.002.004.00076 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 136 exam 1, 2008; UA157.002.004.00077 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 136 exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.004.00078 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 136 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.004.00079 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 136, 2002; UA157.002.004.00080 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 136 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.004.00081 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 exam 2 in class: 3-31-03 takehome: 4-7-03, 2003; UA157.002.004.00082 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 136 final, 2007; UA157.002.004.00083 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 145-01 exam 1, 2008; UA157.002.004.00084 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 145-02 exam 1, 2008; UA157.002.004.00085 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 145 exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.004.00086 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 145 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.004.00087 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 145-01 exam II, 2008; UA157.002.004.00088 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 145-02 exam II, 2008; UA157.002.004.00089 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 146 exm 1, 2008; UA157.002.004.00090 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 146 exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.004.00091 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 146 exam 1 2-12-03, 2003; UA157.002.004.00092 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 146 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.004.00093 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 146 exam 2, 2003; UA157.002.004.00094 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 146 exam 3, 2004; UA157.002.004.00095 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 146 exam 3, 2003; UA157.002.004.00096 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 146 exam 4, 2004; UA157.002.004.00097 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 146 final, 2007; UA157.002.004.00098 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 158 exam 1 sp, 2006; UA157.002.004.00099 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - M. 158 1, 2004; UA157.002.004.00100 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 158 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.004.00101 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 158 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.004.00102 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 159 exam 2 sp06, 2006; UA157.002.004.00103 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 158 exam 2, 2003; UA157.002.004.00104 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 158 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.004.00105 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 161 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.004.00106 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 161 exam 1, 2001; UA157.002.004.00107 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 161 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.004.00108 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 161 final, 2007; UA157.002.004.00109 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 161 final, 2004; UA157.002.004.00110 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 161 final exam, 2003; UA157.002.004.00111 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 162 exam I + solutions sp. 03, 2003; UA157.002.004.00112 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 162 exam 2, 2006; UA157.002.004.00113 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 162 exam II + solutions sp, 2003; UA157.002.004.00114 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 162 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.004.00115 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 162 final exam spring 2004, UA157.002.004.00116 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 162 final exam + solutions, 2003; UA157.002.004.00117 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 215 exam 1, 2005; UA157.002.004.00118 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 215 exam 2, 2005; UA157.002.004.00119 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 215 exam 3, 2005; UA157.002.004.00120 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 216 exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.004.00121 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 217 1st exam, 2008; UA157.002.004.00122 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
- Review materials, 2000 -- 2008; UA157.003; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains materials used for review of mathematic concepts in preparation for exams.
  This series is arranged by course number.
  - Math 24 - reviews, 2000 -- 2008; UA157.003.004.00123 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 5 - reviews, 2000 -- 2007; UA157.003.004.00124 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 6 - reviews, 2000 -- 2006; UA157.003.004.00125 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 8 - reviews, 2003; UA157.003.004.00126 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 9 - reviews, 2005; UA157.003.004.00127 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 11 - reviews, 2000 -- 2007; UA157.003.004.00128 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 11 - reviews (cont'D), 2005; UA157.003.004.00129 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 12 - reviews, 2000 -- 2003; UA157.003.004.00130 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 13 - reviews, 2002 -- 2007; UA157.003.004.00131 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 17 exam reviews, 2002; UA157.003.004.00132 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 22 - reviews, 2002 -- 2008; UA157.003.004.00133 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 38 - reviews, 2002; UA157.003.004.00134 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 46 - reviews, 2003 -- 2007; UA157.003.004.00135 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 135 - reviews, 2007; UA157.003.004.00136 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 145 - reviews, 2007; UA157.003.004.00137 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
  - Math 158 - reviews, 2005; UA157.003.004.00138 (Box UA157 Shared 2)
- Textbooks, 1918 -- 2000; 1952 -- 2000; UA157.004; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains lists of textbooks used by the department and a sample of an early textbook.
  Open for research.
  - Freshman Mathematics, 1918; UA157.004.005.00004; Ransom, William R. (Box UA157 Shared 1)
    Donated by Allan Chemow.
  - Textbook lists, 1952 -- 2000; UA157.004.005.00005 (Box UA157 Shared 1)
    Fall 1952-Fall 2000.